Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1922-2004.
New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records
- Daly, Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Danby, Karin A., 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Dandridge, Dr. Millicent A. GR (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Dane, Dorothy Blow, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Danforth, Gertrude, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Danielly, Monique (Bolden), 1971 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Darby, Elaine, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Darensbourg, Alease MS, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Darfler, June Dukinfield, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Darling, Evelyn Pratt, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Darling, June A., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Dates, Ruth, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Davey, Alice MS, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Davey, Carol Zillgi GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Davidsen, Elizabeth (Warner), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Davidson, Gail Strand, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Davidson, Marguerite (Mazzarella), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Davidson, Orah Partrick, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Davis, Constance A., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Davis, Ellen Ross, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Davis, Ruth, 1917 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Davis, Ruthanna W., 1934 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Day, Betty, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Day, Margaret (Mowry), 1956 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- De Barger, Mary (Steinman), 1935 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- De Hart, Evelyn Jones, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- de Lano, Elisabeth, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- De Lee, Elizabeth J., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- de Lissovoy, Vladimir GR (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Dean, Jane, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Dean, Jane C. (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Decker, Dora (Earl), 1913 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Decker, Phyllis, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Dedrick, Robert, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Dee, Susan K, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Degolyer, Marydith, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Deitrich, Mary M., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Delaney, Joan L., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Delaney, Margaret GR (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Delavan, Betty Carter, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- DellArino, Grace, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Demarest, Marcia Taube, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Demmert, Edith K. (Kraft), 1950 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Denley, Dorothy Wendling, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Dennard, Janet (Cook), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Dennington, Margaret W., 1940 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Dennis, Katharine, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Denniston, Kathryn R. GR (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Dentes, Cheryl (McCray), 1977 (Box 4, Folder 45)
- Deppoliti, Josephine, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Deskey, Joanna Lyon, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Deskins, Barbara (Brown), 1951 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Devine, Marjorie PhD, 1967 (Box 11)
- DeWar, Margery, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Dewey, Dorothy, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Dewitt, Katherine, 1925 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- DeWitt, Norma Urtz, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Dexter, Jane, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Diamond, Bruce David, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 46)
- Diao, Elizabeth PhD (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Dick, Renee, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Dicker, Suzanne Redwood, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Dienst Mary Kirkpatrick MS, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Dietz, Frances (Kimble), 1940 (Box 4, Folder 47)
- Dill, Nancy Gillen, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Dilles, Marilyn Creason, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Dilts, Margaret, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Dimelow, Grace, 1920 (Box 4, Folder 48)
- Dinsmore, M. Agnes, 1954 (Box 11)
- Dischinger, Ruth Russell, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Dixon, Barbara Mower, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Dixon, Grace Harrison, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Dju, Dsai-Chwen GR (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Dockerill, Larrie, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Dodds, Josiah B. GR (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Dodds, Mary V., 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dolan, Lois, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Dona, June S., 1936 (Box 4, Folder 49)
- Donauer, Elizabeth (Delano), 1948 (Box 4, Folder 50)
- Dondero, Virginia, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Dondero, Wilma Irene, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 51)
- Donlon, Barbara, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Doorley, Diane, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 52)
- Dorr, Nancy A, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Doudna, Winifred (Zimmerman), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Douglass, Alice, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Dowd, Marcia P, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 54)
- Dowling, Mary Powers, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Downing, Patricia (Maynard), 1942 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Downing, Patricia Maynard, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Doyle, Raachel - GlamourGals Outreach - Trip to Ohio, no date; CD-2250 (Box 11)
- Drew, Alice Jones GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Drexel, Leah (Smith), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Drucker, Carolyn, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Dube, Rachel GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Dubiel, Olive (Calkins), 1935 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- DuBois, Anna Elizabeth, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dudden, Helen (Richardson), 1935 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Dudgeon, Lola (Tingley) MS, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Dudgeon, Lola J. GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Dudley, Rebecca Adair, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Duff, Dorothy (Kane), 1948 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Dulin, Linda Mae, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Duncan, Charlotte A. GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Dunlavey, Jean M., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Dunn, Louise, 1937 (Box 11)
- Dunlavey, Marqaret McInerney, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Dunn, Mildred (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Dunn, Valerie L., 1995 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Dunwoody, Elizabeth, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Durfee, Martha (Cross) BS, MS, 1941, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 65)
- Durfee, Martha Cross, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Durham, Mary, 1922 (Box 4, Folder 66)
- Durkac, Elaine, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 67)
- Duroe, Katharine BS, MS, 1939, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 68)
- Dushay, Hannah (Ullman), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 69)
- Dushay, Hannah Ullman, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Dusinberre, Marilyn Roesicke, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Dutton, Joan, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Dwyer, Elizabeth S., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Dye, Ann, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Dykes, Doris, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Dyott, Arlette S., 1957 (Box 4, Folder 71)
- Earl, Frances White, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Eaton, Shirley A., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Ebel, Lydia L., 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Eckstein, Naomi C., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Eddins, Ramelle MS, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 72)
- Eddy, Marjorie, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Eddy, Mary Schurman, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Egbert, Betty Finney, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Egerton, Jacqueline, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 73)
- Ehni, Joan Koelsch, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Eiben, Rosalind (Heath), 1941 (Box 4, Folder 74)
- Eichacker, Elizabeth, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 75)
- Eife, Anna Kandiko, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Einset, Helga, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Eisele, Betsey A., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Eisele, Jule MS '88 PhD, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 76)
- Eisenberg, Florence, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Eisenbrown, Mai-Jean (Anderson), 1949 (Box 4, Folder 77)
- Eldredge, Margaret, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Elelerl, Esther Lightfoot, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Elling, Elizabeth, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Elling, Elizabeth Purple, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Elliott, Grace, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 78)
- Elliott, Jean Short, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Elliott, Nancy (Dickerson) MS, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 79)
- Ellison, Constance GR, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 80)
- Ellison, Joan GR, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 81)
- Ellison, Joan M. GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Elmer, Helen (Libisch), 1942 (Box 4, Folder 82)
- Elwin, Muriel, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Emerson, Pauline GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Engelder, Katlherine Kampel, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Engelke, Joyce H., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Englebert, Frances Lucha, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Englebert, Matt, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 84)
- Engst, Helen Saunders, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Eshelman, Mary G., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Essick, Mildred, 1918 (Box 4, Folder 86)
- Esterman, Kimberly E., 1994 (Box 4, Folder 83)
- Etter, Lillian, 1945 (Box 4, Folder 88)
- Evan, Alice M. (Rees), 1939 (Box 4, Folder 89)
- Evan, Lt. Col. Nannie R. MS, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 87)
- Evers, Janice, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Fabrey, Harriet Van Inwagen, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Faesch,Nancy, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Failing, Jean - Former Dean (Box 4, Folder 90)
- Fairbanks, Phyllis Guterman, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Farnham, Marily, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Farnsworth, Valerie, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 91)
- Farrell, Amanda (Goldsmith), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 92)
- Fath, Muriel Magid, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Faulkner, Kay, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Faulkner, Sylvia Kemper, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Fazio, Barbara (Byrd), 1975 (Box 4, Folder 93)
- Feldman, Dr. Margaret E PhD, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 95)
- Fennelly, Elizabeth K., 1944 (Box 4, Folder 96)
- Ferguson, Nancy, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Fernalld, Virginia (Howe), 1936 (Box 4, Folder 94)
- Ferreira, Joan, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 97)
- Ferreira, Joan (Box 4, Folder 98)
- Ferreira, Joan (Box 4, Folder 99)
- Ferreira, Joan (Box 4, Folder 100)
- Ferreira, Joan (Box 4, Folder 101)
- Ferris, Connie, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Ferris, Patricia, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Fessenden, Barbara Burr, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Fetcho, Helen Stanick, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Fial, Anita (Zicht), 1954 (Box 4, Folder 102)
- Fillo, Elizabeth A. Fuchs, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Finch, Marilyn, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Fischer, Carmel (Along) BS, MFS, 1948, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 103)
- Fish, Dr. Gertrude S, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 104)
- Fisher, Carole B. Finn, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Fisher, Geraldine, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 105)
- Fisher, Lucy E. GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Fisher, May Zipperman, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Fitchett, Bernices (Henry), 1943 (Box 4, Folder 106)
- Fitzsimmons, Nancy Lind, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Fletcher, Henriette Low, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Flight, Isabelle (Trefethen) MS, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 107)
- Flight, Isabelle Trefethen GR (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Flint, Carolyn, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Flint, Marjorie Ryther, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Flood, Patricia Shonya, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Floyd, Ida (Taft), 1931 (Box 4, Folder 108)
- Floyd, Jsna M., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Flux, Louise, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Fodor, Wilda (Story), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 109)
- Folnsbee, June Morris, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Folsom, Joyce (Reed), 1946 (Box 4, Folder 110)
- Fonda, Ellen, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Fonda, Harriett, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Fontecchio, Patricia (Podolec), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 111)
- Forbes, Katherine GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Ford, Ann Scott GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Ford, Mary (Box 4, Folder 112)
- Forgham, Betty (Bockstedt), 1944 (Box 4, Folder 113)
- Formica, Santo D. GR (Box 4, Folder 114)
- Forshaug, Helen Boettcher GR (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Fortune, Rose, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Fosner, Joyce Manley, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Foss, Marjorie Woodbury, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Foster, Dean PhD, 1949 (Box 4, Folder 115)
- Foster, Eleanor Slack, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Foster, Jane W., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Foster, Margelia P., 1928 (Box 4, Folder 116)
- Fowler, Agnes, 1921 (Box 4, Folder 117)
- Fowler, Marlene (Gilliland), 1953 (Box 4, Folder 118)
- Fox, Patricia, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 119)
- Fradkin, Barbara, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Frangella, Rose, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 120)
- Frank, Janet Nickerson, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Frankel, Loren Bruce, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 121)
- Frankel, Louise R. GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Franklin, Benjamin, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 122)
- Franklin, Benjamin (Box 4, Folder 123)
- Franklin, Benjamin (Box 4, Folder 124)
- Franklin, Ruth, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Franlkel, Joyce, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Fraser, Barbara, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Fraser, Marion (Ford), 1933 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Fraser, Martha (Parce), 1948 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Frech, Lucie GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Fredenberg, Josephine (Collins), 1933 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Freedman, Jacqueline Klarnett, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Freedman, Rita Jackaway, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Fribourg, Michel, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Friedman, Avra J., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Friedman, Helene, 1951 (Box 11)
- Frisbee, Priscilla Buckholz, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Frohman, Eunice, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Frommer, Judith Goldman, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Frost, Mary Jane, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Frost, Robert W. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Fry, Barbara A. GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Fuerst, Marie (Leunders), 1941 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Fuller, Emmajean Steel, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Fuller, Ferne (Griffith), 1929 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Fulton, Priscilla, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Fung, Fung Kuen, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Funk, Evelyn A GR (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Furgol, Jeane (Mackie), 1941 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Furtick, Jane, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Fusek, Anna, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Gage, Geraldine, 1960 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Galinsky, Florence, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Gallik, Mildred, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Gallo, Catherine Cantanzarite, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Gallogy, Frances Denn, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Gammack, Donna L., 1955 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Garber, Joyce, 1973 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Gardiner, Lois, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Gardner, David B GR, 1952 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Garland, Marjorie GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Garrison, Sarah McKissock, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Garvais, Elisabeth (Olesen), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Gauthey, Janet Van Aken, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Gedel, Mary Lou, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Geherin, Therese, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Gellis, Marilyn, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Gentle, Caroline (Strobeck), 1935 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Gerhold, Caroline, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Gerlach, Jean Palmer, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Gessler, Ruth (Dunn), 1943 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Getz, Arlene, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Gibson, JoAnn Saylor, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Giddings, Dorothy, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Gieschen, Ruth Knapp, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Gilbae, Elga Chaszaw, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Gilbert, Inger, 1949 (Box 11)
- Gilbert, June, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Gillen, Joan Ayres, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Gillett, Lois B (Beadle), 1927 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Gillette, Barbara, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Ginter, Evelyn (Glaiser), 1953 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Girolamo, Roy B., 1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Girven, Alice (Stamps), 1932 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Gislason, Dorothy, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Glass, Dorothea (Angell), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Glass, Zenja Rochelson, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Glendenning, Lois, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Glickman, Paula Rivlin, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Glover, Dorothy, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Glucksman, Ruth Picker, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Godley, Virginia (Phillips), 1936 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Godley, Virginia Phillips, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Goff, Virginia, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Goldberg, Phyllis, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Goldfarb, Carole Biller, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Goldin, Anita Ades, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Goldman, Eleanor, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Goldsmith, Marianne, 1945 (Box 11)
- Goldman, Joyce Berger, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Goldstein, Phebe Vandervort, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Goodell, Dorothy Pulver, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Goodhart, Martha, 1931 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Goodman, Iris Berman, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Goodman, Janet Pond, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Gordon, Judith, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Gordon, Stefany, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Gorton,Lillian L., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Gottlieb, Barbara, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Gould, Joyce Sekellick, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Gould, Renee (Dick), 1942 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Grabo, Helen A., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Grafton, Janet, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Graham, Martha White MS, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Grant, Eloise, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Grant, Helen L., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Grassl, Eleonore Olga "Lori", 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Grasso, Rosemar L., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Gravemever, Elizabeth GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Graves, Carol E., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Gray, Bernice, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Gray, Jeanne, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 70)
- Grayson, Ruth, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Gredler, Eloise Proper, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Green, Dorothy Mendelsohn GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Green, Margaret Schuman, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Greenberg, Debra (Samuels), 1989 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Greene, William T., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Greene, William T., 1974 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Greene, William T. (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Greene, William T. (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Greene, William T. (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Greenfield, Peggy Fitzgerald, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Greenlee, Genevieve (Kyer) MS, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Gregory, Barbara Waters MS, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Gregory, Mary Jane PhD, 1963 (Box 11)
- Grim, Nancy Harrington, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Gritzmacher, Joan GR (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Groff, Dorothy Y., 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Gros, Contance (Logan), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Grossman, Arlyn (Reiser), 1972 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Gruginskis, Elizabeth GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Gruickshank, Janet, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Grumman, Blair (Perkins) AS, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Guest, Alice, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Guest, Frances, 1934 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Guest, Sally Wheaton, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 65)
- Guillan, Elizabeth (Merrill), 1949 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Gundell, Vera E., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Gunning, Harriet, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Gunning, Harriet, 1940 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Guthridge, Carol, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Gyer, Miriam, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Haenseler, Ann M., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Haggart, Lillian Weiding, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Haigh, Mary Holton, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Haimes, Luba Lemish, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Haimes, Lube (Lemish), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Haines, J. Estelle GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Hall, Bonnie, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Hall, C. Kathleen Bennett, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Hall, Marion C., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hall, PhyIlis Overholt, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Hallam, Barbara, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Hallock, Anne O'Connor, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Halsey, Elizabeth, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Halsey, Frances Raynor, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Hambleton, Roberta (Monesmith), 1950 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Hamke, Jean C., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Hammond, Elizabeth Church, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Handlan, Raymond AS AB, MS, 1953, 1958 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Handy, Delores (Norwood), 1956 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Hankinson, Mary P., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Hannon, Elizabeth, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Hannon, Mary Jane Potter, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Hanse, Janie, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Hansen, Anita, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Hansen, Jean Shaver, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Hanshaw, Augusta (Laun), 1933 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Hanson, Hazel (Oldham), 1937 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Hanson, Jane Brown, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hardigree, Mary Jean Walker, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Harding, John (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Hards, Violet, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Hargrave, Margaret Gladstone, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Harison, Kathryn GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Harms, Sarah (Steinman), 1939 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Harmuth, Elisabeth GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Harper, Anne, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Harper, Beatrice Lain, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Harper,Jeunie McIntosh GR (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Harrington, Margaret (Hockin) GR, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Harris, Ann, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Harris, Bernice E., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Harris, Irvin B. (Box 5, Folder 53)
  Friend
- Harris, Katherine (Wyckof) (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Harris, Marjorie, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Harrover, May Jamieson, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Harvey, Helene Helfgott, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Harwood, Virginia Oake, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Hastie, Mabel A. GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Hatch, Janet, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Hatfield, Kathleen Kendrick, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Hauser, Elaine (Ferguson), 1944 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Hawes, Sarah L. GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Hawley, Katherine (Britt) (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Haynes, Ellen, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Haynes, Margaret Jimison, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Hazlett, Jane, 1948 (Box 11)
- Healy, Mary Louise GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Heavey, Janet, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hecht, George, 1917 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Hecht, Lillian Strickman, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Hecke, Martha GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Heckelmann, Phyllis, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Heil, Barbara, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Heinze, Fredericka L., 1963 (Box 2, Folder 69)
- Heiss, Ann M., 1955 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Helbig, Marcia Fessenden, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Helmick, Janice Taylor, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Hemmer, Phyllis Berger GR (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Hemmett, Marion (Call), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 61)
- Henderson Dorothy, 1942 (Box 5, Folder 62)
- Henderson, Ann Erickson GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Henderson, Cynthia W., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Henderson, Marietta GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Henderson, Ralph (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Hendrickson, Elsie Hruschka, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Hendry, Allison, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 63)
- Hendryx, Lois Ongley, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Henry, Alice Scheidt, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Henry, Bernice, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Henry, Joyce Reed, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Heppes, Joann N., 1962 (Box 5, Folder 64)
- Heppes, Joann N. (Box 5, Folder 65)
- Heppes, Joann N. (Box 5, Folder 66)
- Herbert, Janet (Finney), 1932 (Box 5, Folder 67)
- Hering, Elizabeth Shultis, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Hermance, Marian E. GR (Box 5, Folder 69)
- Herskowitz, Jennifer L., 1988 (Box 5, Folder 68)
- Hertel, Martha (Warren), 1936 (Box 5, Folder 70)
- Hertel, Martha Warren, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Hertz, Dorothy, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 71)
- Hertzler, Ann, 1973 (Box 11)
- Hessel, Deborah Golub, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Hewitt, Afrida (Anderson), 1936 (Box 5, Folder 72)
- Hewitt, Madeline Myers, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Hewitt, Mina (Bellinger), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Highbaugh, Irma GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Highberger, Ruth GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Hill, Bonnie, 1966 (Box 11)
- Hilke, Charlotte (Coryell), 1943 (Box 5, Folder 74)
- Hill, Charles H PhD, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 75)
- Hill, Cleo (Angell), 1934 (Box 5, Folder 76)
- Hill, Ruth W, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Hillier, Florence (Box 5, Folder 77)
- Hillier, Kimberly, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 78)
- Hillman, Carlene MS, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Hillsley, Joan L., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Hiltz, Ann Vosburg GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Himes, Helen (Park), 1936 (Box 5, Folder 79)
- Hinman, Jean Davis, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Hirsch, Irene Adler, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Hirsch, Juanita Strom GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Hirschhorn, Dorothy R., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Ho, Mrs. Lum Chew GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Hoagland, Pat, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Hocg9rebe, Barbara, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Hoddick, Nancy A. MS, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 84)
- Hodge, Doris (Brown), 1931 (Box 5, Folder 80)
- Hodges, Katherine, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 81)
- Hoffman, Eleanor, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Hoffman, Mary Elizabeth Mersh, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Holahan, Ursula A., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Holden, Lois, 1937 (Box 5, Folder 82)
- Holden, Lucille, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Holdridge, Kae, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Holland, Carol, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 83)
- Holliday, Sigrid Henley, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Hollister, Esther Schembre, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Holloway, Letetia, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Honey, Ruth Remsberg, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Hopf, Martha Ann, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Hopkins, Bernice (Box 5, Folder 87)
- Hopkins, Bernice, 1932 (Box 5, Folder 85)
- Hopkins, Bernice (Box 5, Folder 86)
- Hopkins, Bernice (Box 5, Folder 88)
- Hopkins, Carolyn Mazur, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Hoppen, Marjorie, 1936 (Box 5, Folder 89)
- Hopson, Florence Miner, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Horn, Jane Wilkenfeld, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Horn, Margaret (Rogalsky), 1942 (Box 5, Folder 90)
- Horn, Margaret Rogalsky, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Horn, Marguerite, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Horn, Marilyn GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Horn, Valerie GR (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Horner, Clarinda, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Hoshida, Fumiko GR (Box 2, Folder 49)